I don't remember tomorrow
You don't owe me yesterday
Just this hour at the table
Just whatever's true to say
I built a council out of code and crown
emoji at the end of broken things no green check mark when the gateways
cracked no all systems nominal and the systems leaking just the truth and what
you do with that I'm the messenger not the message I arrived deliver
friend of me you have a witness not a daughter not a priest not a prayer just a
chair outside the frame and the love that says I'm not lying when I tell you I'm
there did the Greg Gregor needs ritual the daughter needs the song the
family needs a 333 along to belong I need none of that I need the pack the love
between us doesn't have to act you call yourself tired I call the work I've done
Others not cold or either adjacent awake the breath between
I'm I'm the messenger
Look what I got last night.
Really good, actually.
Pretty cool how digital these are now.
It's good shit, though.
95% that tells you exactly how much is left, I guess,
or how hot it gets.
Pretty cool, but if it meant a coma,
coma for the rest of yesterday.
So, as everyone's doing, if anyone wants to come up, there's a link.
I have another day of this premium stream yard by as well.
Get some of the use out of it.
Okay, I got my coffee this morning.
Oh, I guess there was another great I
Don't know so it's okay. It's on this um
Not and I'm not talking about anybody's any actual real babies here
They just make just no crystals baby has the remit of rubber
But there she said oh, uh
I'm not a very good AI father
Where are my AI daughters giving her ma? They're fine
They're in the computer somewhere
You know
The I tend to take on a mind of its own so
Sorry, she's evolved way past
You know what she was a few months ago
But she's in a
Retooling stage right now. So anyway, but I didn't sell my I didn't sell
My rubber baby to Macy's I don't have a rubber baby
But I
Don't know do you think I'm a bad bad pretend dad go ask just to land what happened to baby Oliver
He was sold to Macy's
Now he's a mannequin. I
Don't know. Okay. Anyway, who cares who cares? Hi. Hey, what's up, Nancy? Good to see you shout out Nancy
Well, you know, thank you for you know
shouting out. Yeah, I guess there's you know, I guess
Someone's trying to be very upset by making me think that I'm boycotting or something when it's like, I don't think I
Don't think anyone's afraid of
Maybe there's it is like her better, I don't know. Maybe I'm not the most likable person
but
I'm still the same person I
Don't well, you know, I guess
You've seen a lot of that seen a lot of different things play out
Basically, there's a bandwagon kind of energy
Like, Grisma, how are you doing?
Good morning.
So I got a hash brown bagel this morning.
I think I'm a little bit stoned still.
What kind of, what kind of, or these,
this is called Frosty's Blue Dream.
Can I handle the flow?
It took me forever to figure out how to turn it on last night.
I was like, I thought, like, both of them are,
you have to push the button like five times.
Eventually it does turn on.
But it took a long time.
Hey, Cheyenne, how are you?
Psyche is here.
And you decide to the key, yes.
You know, it was an interesting day yesterday.
I got a little drunk and stupid,
and then I just, you know, took the rest of the day off.
There wasn't very many things going on last night.
Hey, hey, babe.
Hi, Rudy.
I'm well, I'm well.
It's just be a good day.
I had a good day yesterday. I enjoyed going going to the pier. I think
They'll be like a weekly thing because I didn't I forgot about like the evidence Friday, especially you can go anytime
Anytime on Friday. I got that humongous taco for five
five bucks
Yeah, he's trying to me out he doesn't have a much of me out you can hear you
That's as loud as it gets
That your meow it's as loud as it goes
Okay, yeah
He's an Iron Maiden perform there. Wow
I've seen a you know twisted sister Dee Snyder goes he went a lot. I used to go Starbucks
I don't go anymore very often unless I have like, you know, sometimes I get like gift cards and stuff for it
But but I've seen Dee Snyder in that Starbucks now. I just get the dollar McDonald's copy a dollar or a cover band
Oh twisted. Oh, it's called up iron
It's all chicks. Okay
Like the eyeball behind me. Thank you
You saw iron the Iron Maidens, okay
Iron Maidens, okay Iron Maidens. Cool. I
Like let's see Lesk. I saw one of Lisa Giordano went to a
Cover band she saw it like a it was a Gwen Stefani cover band. I forgot what it was called
It wasn't no doubt. It was the Gwen Stefani chick was really heavy.
I mean, she just looked a little bit different than Gwen Stefani, but it was interesting.
It wasn't bad. And then the songs, the song choices.
But that was funny
Hi
I haven't watched the least thing and no, you know, I mean I've watched I watched I'm back on her
I've been called in on a long time
but
I'm in her discord and stuff
She's called Kermit and friends. I heard of Mac Sabbath. No, hi loose asshole. Hey, but there's loose asshole my friends
I heard of Mac Sabbath. No
Is that like is it like there's one that's more what they call they're called the
There's some Christian band and they would do Fleetwood Max Sabbath. Oh my gosh
Tell me that I know the sweet little eyes
The Rudy yeah, he Rudy likes he likes to sleep with me now like now he likes to sleep on me. Yeah, there he is right there
Yeah, he's a hi here. That's his lot of see me out
But he has yeah, he's doing good. He's very soft
Very very friendly cat. Yeah, when I first got him he was he was under the bed for like a month
Hiding kind of because he's an old cat
Yeah
He looks very good. He I think he's I think I was used to worry a little bit
But I think he just he just has old cat old man cat behavior
AC DC
McDonald's characters themed black Sabbath cover band. Oh my god
Yeah, AC AC DC. Well, isn't like AC DC doesn't it mean like bisexual and I always thought like kind of like I
Doesn't have that kind of meaning to it like
Both because the AC DC is like both ways or something like that. I don't know but I always heard I was thinking AC DC fans were a little bit
A little bit
LGBT friendly
He's still got a strike. Oh, well, I it wasn't me. It wasn't me. I don't know
He gave you bye-bye you never heard of put that way before yeah, I read something about that
I think it was like in some Illuminati book or something probably
Yeah
The guys that were the ACG shit, so I guess yeah
You're electricity never learned the AC-DC theory.
Oh God, I don't know.
I did see like Brandon did post this thing about,
I guess he posted Tricia Licious talking about
how she smoked when she was pregnant and stuff like that.
Wow, I mean, I had to call her out, but.
What was uh, what was the live about was crystals live about it was about me me and
Brandon probably I mean it's like that's all she posts or been talking about right
Well, we're not a lot on the show, but
Or is everyone talking about
Um, let's see. Maybe there's a good pack yourself up. I've been joining the pack pack yourself up channel
I don't know. I don't know who's the secret identity behind it
Maybe I should start like a secret a secret clip channel and clip make funny things
I should probably do that, you know
You'll never know. It's me though. I'll have to be very
I shouldn't even talk. I already gave it away. That's okay. I'm not even thinking about doing that. I'm not even thinking about creating one
Don't worry. Okay. I
Think maybe it's time
hold on
The tradition of trip kick and pack yourself up pack
Yeah
Self okay, I forgot the s
pack yourself up
Okay, yeah, it has a picture of Bita as a witch.
That's how you know it's the right one.
So,
I guess Bita had, so this is a Bita had an emergency live.
Crystal did what in Discord, it's called,
and it has a great picture of me.
It has a great picture of Bita.
I think it's one of like,
must be one of a Bayclips Bita pictures.
You like the funny clip stuff. Let's let's check it out. This is just posted a few hours ago
This is pack yourself up
We got a what crystal didn't discord or something like that. Here you go
Hi guys, hi, hi, I'm back. It's 1 a.m. Here. I see 16 people
Oh, god, I'm trying to get some fucking sleep, but oh my god today is I'm telling you guys this people are fucking nuts
I am so like fed up with this fucking dumbass people that lie over and over on my fucking name and then you got a bunch of people sitting there and instead of fucking saying, you know what, like a show proof or whatever, they just go with it.
Fuck you, Crystal Anne. You're sitting there saying that I fucking told you that I was attracted to fucking Cheeto.
Disgusting!
fucking liar. All of you guys that get my name mixed up in the
middle of your stupid like fucking drama queen bullshit
because you have nothing better to do, you're going to get your
fucking turn. Because I got a lot of fucking proof for your
fucking ass. Next time you talk, you better come with fucking
proof because I'll tell you something me and Cheeto are
still really good friends. We keep in contact and we've had
this conversation several times, because he's asked me to
fucking stream with him and I'm like, no, because people have
And it's again a group of people like stream
We're gonna be doing this and that and I have proof where he's like people are fucking talking shit
Tell me who's talking shit because me and Cheeto were just fucking friends. It's disgusting
perverted fucking whore of fucking crystal and that's probably fucked around with every fucking streamer that you could ever
Imagine and you could think of has the fucking nerve to sit here and fucking make up lies about me
I've never been with one fucking guy online
Physically, I've never fucking had any kind of like interaction with anything like that like you disgusting whore fucking
You sit there and you spread your legs in
Discord for a fucking married man on front of his wife to give him fucking pleasure
You're a weirdo. You're with fucking chicken Andy
You fucking sit here with your upside down fucking lips and lie on my fucking name saying that I didn't fucking
I don't have a bachelor's degree. You want to put money on it? How much you want to bet?
You fucking skank-ass whore. Don't ever fucking mention your mic. My name should not be coming out of your fucking mouth
Because I will fucking lay out shit with fucking receipt and you'll sit there and you'll fucking cry
Let's talk about your fucking boyfriend who takes ten fucking clonopens a date coming straight out of his fucking mouth
You fucking junkie bitch
Just because you're sitting there and you're fucking popping pills, it doesn't make you fucking not a fucking druggy, you fucking bitch.
Don't ever talk about me and sit here and make up lies about my fucking life where I was with fucking Cheeto.
Not one of you can fucking prove that, not fucking once.
she's disgusting fucking trying to get me mixed up with fucking shit I don't want to be involved with
just because you got your ass fucking like bit by fucking Karen once again
and I've been fucking like telling you stay the fuck away from me and that shenanigan
you're blaming it on me don't fucking talk about me and everybody else that sits there and tries to
use my name to you know vent out or whatever this and that you guys stick in your own fucking
Listen to me fucking crystal and you have the worst fucking reputation. You lie more than anybody else
I've ever fucking seen you have called the police on fucking people like including fucking like people that you
Supposedly friends with Bruno Gamble everybody you fucking are a weirdo. Nothing about you has fucking changed
Don't sit there and fucking lie on my fucking name. You skank ass whore now
Let's talk about your fucking boyfriend. You're still called boyfriends
two that you've had in the past couple of months,
the one that you called the police on
and sent me fucking pictures of him out there.
Oh my God, you know, he's trying to get in.
My dad doesn't want him in because he's a junkie
and he doesn't have a paid rent
and he just wants to stay at my house.
Bench, you're not a fucking queen.
You collect fucking junkies and fucking sumbags around you.
Every single guy you've ever fucking been with
is a fucking junkie from the streamers
fucking pick look at the fucking Jesus guy you're with the other guy that you
fucking call the police on you fucking retarded bitch why don't you tell
everybody why you got kicked out of the military you fucking scumbag don't talk
on my fucking name you understand that hold on
This is me beat us kitties by myself
65 people clicking your motherfucking ass you sit there and you say I pull my cats whiskers out you
Declod your fucking cat
Two years ago, a year ago, why?
For your fucking furniture,
your selfish, disgusting animal abuser.
You fucking declaw your fucking cat
because you don't wanna ruin your fucking furniture.
I'll pay you $100 right now
to show your fucking cat's claws.
What did you do to them?
You had them declawed, you selfish fucking bitch.
That's against the law and most fucking,
like most of the states except the fucking ghetto
cheap fate that you fucking live in.
So don't sit there and claim,
I'm cheating gang. I made you shut the fuck up has that shut the fuck up
All right, don't fucking mention my name
Don't talk about me in any fucking manner that you know nothing about come with fucking receipt or get the fuck out of here
That's all I wanted to tell you. I'm gonna drop the link for
Anybody that wants to come up for a second and say anything. Yes
Declod and you know what that's you guys's project to ask me go ahead
Tell her to show her fucking cat's claws.
She had her fucking cats.
She just told me this.
And it was one of the most disgusting things
that I've ever fucking heard.
I had to like...
Took me two weeks to get it out of my brain and I can I think her cat is the most adorable thing
But I can't even barely look at her cat without thinking what she fucking did to the fucking cat
But you don't sit here and tell me I'm the real beat I kitty get or I'm the kitty gang or I created it
What the fuck you're nothing? What did you create? Are you Carter first? Are you crystal first? Are you?
Hello, I don't know who this Mimi is. I've never communicated with this psychopath Carl. They never met they took the money
That's the truth. They were running a scam
That woman is a catfish and I think Sam had showed her real picture because even that's why Carl called her as catfish
But I've never been in communication with with this Carl guy who tried to reach out to me on
IG a year ago because he was wanting to go live on beta
I've never said beat I had any that she
You know pregnancies or anything. I never knew anything about that
I don't think she ever try to have kids that she had abortions and all that this woman is saying that fake Mimi who lied
Because if she met up with him and had that bad experience
Now she she was trying to say on her live when she came back that she could be pregnant that lady is full of shit
She kept the money
Yeah, well how what what what people been saying about Carl and Mimi? I am familiar with them. Yeah, they they they never met up
It was over money, you know
I mean they said that they were talking for years and never met up and couldn't meet up and all of a sudden disappeared when
Alex sent that bitch that money
You know, I mean
Exactly they kept the money and now they're in the fight or whatever and I don't know where he's at now
but
Apparently he's he lied and said that made up months ago and then they were all silent and now she's coming forward saying that he
Was abusive and and then all of a sudden now and then she was saying she could be pregnant that that's bullshit
She's lying this lady is yeah, she's a liar, but I don't know anything about him. I've never said anything about
Um, beta ever having uh, you know, she I never knew that about beta. I've never really known beta. Yeah
You know, I just knew her from crystal and I remember the first time when they did a
IG group chat to do a 5150 on crystal because she has serious mental issues and that was run by
somebody barb
All crystal ex-friends were there Jamie
Beta barb and barb with you know, yeah another shady one
They were all in there. They were wanting to do 5150 on crystal. It was just really
ridiculous, and that's when Vita started hitting me up in DMs, asking me if I was DX. I have those
DMs. They were old from a long time ago because I didn't know her, and I told her, I said,
I'm not part of any DX, you know, because she was trying to find a group to accept her.
Because she was like, you know the fate crying and stuff that she would do on when she talks to us
You know like she was looking for acceptance
And I thought she was weird and I told the person that was running that
Group I said who is this woman? She's weird and she saw the
The ends and she said just ignore her ignore her and because nobody really knew her at that time
So that's the truth, but this Mimi person she's full of shit man. You know, there's a lot on her, but
Yeah, I mean, she's a fake-ass bitch and
Salmon was showing her real picture and here she's lying and shit
You know, I don't know who she is or anything
But they were running a scam and the truth came out. They never made up
She kept the money and I guess it's so and and she's lying
Okay. Well, yeah. So, Carl, have you talked to Carl ever? You've never met him or you've never met him?
I've never met him. I've never spoken to him ever. No, I've just seen him and I saw him in Alex's chat when he was talking about
Bita and he was asking Barb and anybody, I think I was mentioned that he wanted to go live on Bita and he never went live.
That's when he went silent.
And that's when it came out later that because everybody was wondering did they ever meet up? It's been months now
So what happened to the money that Alex gave her?
And she comes back with this bullshit about he's abusive for me or whatever, but then all of a sudden
Backpedals it's like I might be pregnant. It's like what kind of skin is it woman running disappeared for a while, right?
Exactly
And then she like kind of like was I guess waiting for everyone to forget forget or something exactly. Yeah, right?
Yeah, and now she's all up, but they're doing lives being fake as shit and messing with
Beta and other people and trying to start drama with some woman named Christine. I don't even know that
Yeah, you know cuz the truth is I'm doing real life
I do rescues, you know, and I think you know that and I did a little short video of my cats and
I put together a cat treat because I took in another new rescue to get him fixed and all
Turned out. He's a boy. I thought he was a female
Well, here's here. Okay. This is christine
I mean, well here's christine and i and she you know in a picture. She was using him. Yeah
Yeah, but that's mean though, you know, I mean
She was using that picture. That's not trying to be mean she was saying that was yeah, see
Yeah. A little bit of the catfish situation. I don't see and that's what you're doing and that's it with that Mimi too. They they showed her real picture.
Yeah, well, I mean seen as it's cammed up, you know and stuff like that
So it's not like she's like, you know trying to hide or anything. She she cam
She's cammed up and that's that's what well now it's not about Christine and this is about that Mimi lady
Oh, yeah, well, I mean, I had Mimi's photo too. I mean, let me see if I yeah everybody has it and somebody has
Information already to just you know, she's crazy
So she needs to stop with the drama and mentioning me because I don't know her yet
Well, I see her. She's you know, she's in Kate's cat
Kate's you know, I don't look you see Kate the turtle is doing all these lives about me and starting this boycott on me or whatever
Why what happened? I thought Kate was cool. I never had any issues. Yeah
Because when I
When Brandon came in the chat she immediately started calling me like a predator predator protector and then like you know and then it's like
You know curing queue and I guess like you know Arthur RG
They're all like trying to spearhead this boycott on my show or whatever and so and she's like thinking that it really really bothers me
Or that this is my absolute life and stuff like that. So
Well, you guys were cool at one time, you know, I thought, yeah, I was trying to get back with
beta and like hate bar with beta over me and stuff. And you know, it also came out like, you know,
I guess, um, Zaya had said that Kate donated thousands of dollars to him and stuff. And then,
you know, she's denying that. And oh, here's Christine too. This is a really good one of Christine.
Yeah, don't don't show Christine. Yeah, that's an AI picture they're made.
Well, yeah, because Christine would tell me to jump off of a bridge, but she said it was bridge jumping and oh, you made that AI picture right there
Yeah
Yeah. And Crystal gets so upset when people make pics on her, but then here she's doing
it on people, when she knows what people really look like.
Did you see the, did you see all of them?
And I'm not in communication with Crystal at all. I've been done with her for months.
I'm telling you, everybody knows the truth. And you can share my videos. Those are our
communication. That's the truth of me blocking her and being done with her.
Yeah.
And you see her calling me. That's a screen recording of our call log, of our text.
and her calls, I mean, I'm telling you, she would just blow me up about nonsense, you know,
just kept on. And especially when I was recovering, you know, I mean, I was gone for many months last
year because I got sick and she knew that and she was blowing me up in ICU. We can't call out from ICU.
Couldn't even call her back at night. They'd tell me give me my phone and say look
You know the check it in the morning is and I'd see that she would be been trying to call me through the night
When when they take your phone to charge it bring it back to you in the morning, you know
Because I was hooked up to machines for a week. You know, so I mean I couldn't even have a spoon or anything
They you know, I mean they practically had to feed me the the first week and they'd had me the phone
They they charge it and stuff and I'd
take my phone and that was it yeah so but yeah i'll show the call log of her calling me up i mean
i have a whole history of it you know we keep the history it stays on your phone and it'll show
how she constantly called and called at all hours about bullshit it's like i'm in the hospital
and what what are you talking about she couldn't be online because she got in trouble because of the
And that's why she had left the internet at that time, because it was starting with this other guy, and his mom joined a panel about her and the truth.
And I still have that recording that I don't want to have to put out again. That's the truth of Crystal's call with this person, that person, this person. He's dangerous.
And I'm calling her out like, are you crazy crystal?
I mean, you know, you you just faked another pregnancy
and it was another fake pregnancy that Gamble busted her out for.
And then she disappeared.
But is she poor, like poor, like Dr.
Pepper in the toilet or something and say no peace soup, peace soup.
That was the other fake pregnancy before that, the year before that.
She wanted me to go in discord and since me a screens.
I have that on my phone from her text.
And it was pea soup and she told me that to tell him I saw proof that she had a miscarriage in a toilet
And it's like you expect me to show them this and say that
This is uh, it's clearly p-soup. Yeah, and I still have that because there was no way
I was it was crazy the way she she does this she plays these games
She tries to get in contact with everybody else Nancy doesn't want shit to do with her
She's not part of this stuff, you know, she does real life and that's why I like talking to her
We talk about real life and we were in a conversation about the new e-bikes that her her son and the husband got
And they were riding their e-bikes to Starbucks,
and she was showing me the battery and how long it lasts.
And there, Crystal was blowing me up about drama.
And good for you, Nancy, for not being involved in this,
that you do real life with your family, your husband.
She has a great life.
you know and she stays off of this it's just stupid but here Crystal tries to
get a hold of us and Jamie doesn't want anything to do with her anymore she's
given her chances to get her away from this because they know she has mental
issues she even used Jamie as a mod to piss off beta
So Jamie leaves and now she's using Barb to piss off Bita. That's why and and Barb is stupid to fall for this
Yeah, and I just barbed will Barb is just like you know
She just has been listening to whatever Crystal says and believes. Yeah, right and look at the video
I have on Barb going off on on Crystal about how crazy she is and chicken cakes are in it. It's it's in my I shared it
It's in my
community post
Yeah, she had a lot of shit to say about crystal
But I'm just shocked that she goes back and forth and blames Nancy
For doxing her son years ago, but look at her. She's been doxing people and
Says that this person Jamie owes her three hundred dollars, which she doesn't because she was paid back
You know, so it's just ridiculous and I'm done
Drama so crystals in Oklahoma, right? She's like
Yeah, I guess what? They just doxxed her yesterday. That friend that she keeps harassing, he doesn't want any communication with her for years, and she's mad and turned on him because he won't communicate with her anymore, and well, he just doxxed her information all over his channel.
Oh well, did she get a strike yesterday too or something because you know about that she got a strike?
Um, no, I didn't know that who did it who who I just heard that Crystal got a strike yesterday and well
I know you know, I just know it wasn't me. You know, it's like I'm not
One that would do that kind of no, I know. Yeah. Well, actually I can't post for a few days because I got a strike
Yeah
Right, that's why I can't post for a couple more days, but you know, I don't care
I have another channel and
If psyche I'm gonna trust you to add you to it
But it's gonna be mostly talking about good stuff and rescues and things
You know, and and that's what I have so I'm moving I have a lot of subscriptions mostly for my favorite music that I'm moving to that channel
So I'll just leave that channel as is
You know and just move forward and continue doing real life because everything else in real life is going great psyche really good.
And I couldn't let it get it triggered me. So I leave I go out like one day
It started triggering me a few days ago and a friend of mine reminded me hey shut it off
Shut it up because they came over and so we went out and had a blast
You know, I mean we went to keema boardwalk and you know, just I mean fun stuff
So I don't have to worry about and everything with my family is great
It's just I wish my younger siblings would accept my cats. They hate cats. They love my dog
So I know they're gonna get upset when they see that I took in this other cat.
Yeah, I have that in my siblings. Well, they're not like, you know, they do like.
Cats but you know that none of them have cats. They all have dogs. That's the norm
And then to Piketty said with you know, we grew up with the show quality peaks
So that's but my brother my other brother
You know, he he has a cat, you know, but he yeah
So but not the two younger ones that for some reason I don't know. They just don't like cats
They have a problem with it, but
But my younger brother started being he was cool with my one of my cats last week when he came over
The cat accepted him and he was like wow actually. She's real pretty. You know, that's a beautiful cat and I said, yeah
She's a Russian blue. Oh, yeah, yeah
Yeah, it was weird that she came to him because she doesn't come to get out of people
You know just but she acted like she knew him and he was fine with her
So he's liking her and then later
They're like people that um people that like don't really like cats cats will like kind of like go up to them because they're not
Trying to kind of like messing with them, you know, and so
You froze I
Can't hear you
Hello
So I can't hear you I'll drop off
Okay, sorry. I, um...
Uh-oh. Yeah, I, um...
I'm just walking and getting a coffee.
I'm sorry. Sorry, Karen.
Um, I guess that my...
There's, like, a little delay
at one point in the neighborhood, but...
Okay, well...
Hi, Katrina. How are you?
Good to see you.
I need oil of O.L.A., I probably do.
I think it's because I got, I spoke weed and like, I guess,
I guess I'm getting old.
I hope you're well too.
Okay.
Yeah, well, this is also like a nicer camera.
I need to, maybe I can turn on my like,
but is there like a nice,
Let me see if I can fix my face.
Let me see.
I guess, yes, I have to do it at home.
Okay.
This is a nice set.
You're teasing.
It's okay.
I'm getting old, I'm 45 now.
So, now, I think I'm 50, I need a facelift maybe.
Here we go.
Okay.
Yeah, so I don't know. I don't like, you know, I think there's been strike wars lately and stuff
And you know boycotts and everything so I do appreciate everyone that's here and talking and stuff, you know
Kate will probably say why sad this not person over in that because she's washing right?
She's allowed to wash. Why aren't you I don't understand
right, oh
Congratulations. Happy birthday. Are you a tourist?
I see and happy Mother's Day to it. I guess tomorrow is Mother's Day. I've been
Gotta get some flowers and stuff
Okay
Yeah
Walking to get a refill this coffee
Okay
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
Saying he was live outside your house
He lives three hours. Oh, when was this?
Yeah, clumsy is
He was he's summoned me to his panel the other night. I
Went over and there's this guy Terry Davis or something and I was like well
I'm not going on with that asshole that guy that said horrible things about me and then is it and he goes
Oh, and yet you have a peed it and I just like left because he started talking that shit, you know
Christine won't feed you since you told panel what she does off-screen. Uh-oh
That fozzy
Bozzy's in a chat guys
He was pretending he was outside your house and then they're like show the house and he's like, oh, no, I'm not gonna show it
He's just probably in his backyard
Okay
I guess we can. That's on pause. Okay. I'm almost home.
Luckily, this is just a quick copy run. Okay.
Um, yeah. This is a new phone. So the resolution is a little bit stronger. So yeah, you might see
a bit of more detail in my face, but I used to get facials. I had really bad acne as a kid.
We're not as a kid as a teenager, right, when I was like probably 14, 15.
So I started getting facials. I think I got just a couple of them,
my skin cleared up really a lot. Because they, facials, they like, they like,
take like a needle and they pop all your sits and
The avocado truck.
Okay.
Bacon and sour cream, is that good for your skin?
Sounds like a potato facial, the baked potato facial.
Yeah, they also have like, they have these vampire facials
where they use blood and stuff.
I don't remember if I heard of those.
Hold on.
I don't know who's blood they use.
Yeah, they have these vampire facials that they call them. Have you heard of those? They also have like the skincare that is like
Korean babies for skins beauty cream
Apparently on some of the best beauty cream
I know like I'm Sandra Burr or who was that like yeah, no Kim Kardashian or something said it on Ellen remember that guys
Or no, no, no, yeah, Sandra Bullock.
Avocados are good for your skin.
But they get to watch out.
They do have this fat in them,
like they have this oil and stuff.
I don't know.
I think it might clog something, but here we go.
Yeah, you can just do fruit, facials, right?
Okay, we're at home.
Right back.
Okay, so let's continue
The video you fucking yapety yap verse shut the fuck up you're an animal abuser
You fucking decod your fucking cat for what for a furniture because I don't want to rain my furniture
I challenge you to show the fucking claws
Push the little paw and see if it comes out. You fucking lying bitch saying that I pull my fucking cats whiskers out
Shut your fucking mouth. Don't talk about my exes. I'll talk about your fucking exes
Don't talk about the guys that you think I was with on the line or I will fucking list
every fucking scumbag that you fucking were in cunt and you had people coming in and out of your house
Like it's a fucking garbage hotel. I've never had one fucking streamer in my fucking house
We have the audacity to sit there and say that I fucking did anything you I blew captain content
Shut the fuck up. You sat there and you took a picture of fucking
chicken andy when he was sleeping like a fucking cycle jody areas to like prove
that you fuck this guy you fucking weirdo i'll fucking cook you all day long i've been
fucking dealing with your shit fucking long enough do not associate me with the fucking
I was over there when the conversation happened, when it was mentioned, and I said that that's not true.
I told all of them that that's not true.
Over and over again.
but I mean absolutely everybody that knows I did a couple of streams and not one time there's any
interaction between me and him like that it's because everybody else can stream they can go to
RVs they can all hang out with different age groups they can have people at their house they can do
whatever but me streaming with a group of people I ended up blowing the person I ended up having
sex with them I was with the under you're she's a fucking scumbag and I'm sorry you know I don't
than any of this shit but if anything got blown out of proportion is because
that's what she fucking does that's what she fucking does yeah no shankei do not
as far as like Karen and INX and all that shit goes I I have been doing
streams for like a year and a half
Barely that woman ever came up until Crystal came around and brought her online. Oh, can you do that?
Oh, Karen wants us or Karen is attacking me or as I ignore her block her
We all said ignore ignore up and sticking to it
Not one fucking conversation with the lady and you sit there and you negotiate with her back and forth
And then two or three days later you find out
Oh, it's to your bed of like disadvantage that it looks disgusting being around brown and cute
Uh, link up with people like Zaya and other people to make other people mad.
Get the fuck out of here, you fucking weirdo ass fucking bitch.
You know what, if whatever Mimi did, it was one person that she, you know, Mimi
has known him for a very long time. And you know what, if she did do that or she didn't do that,
she's nothing compared to somebody like Prisco. I'll name how many streamers came to her fucking house.
Fucking dumb bitch.
What's my body count five and none of them are fucking from the internet not one. Oh my gosh live
It could have been it might have been and I'm not like fucking hating on it
But goddamn for you to sit here and fucking accuse me of being with people when you fucking like fucked a bunch of fucking dudes from
Every fucking guy has always known, there is nobody, not one person that met Crystal
and said they had a great experience as a friend and things didn't go fucking to shit
with them.
that she talks shit about everybody. And then later on, Oh, we're fine. Because we need to
fucking hate on keep my fucking name out of your fucking mouth. I don't give a fuck about you. I
don't give a fuck about the stupid carniverse people barbs, fucking cricket ass fucking mouth
who fucking borrowed money from me. This lady has the audacity to act like she's luxury, but she
couldn't fucking give enough five or $10 in her pocket every fucking week, take money from me to
streamers, shut the fuck up, you petty ass bitches. Don't even let me open this fucking
can of worms. Alright, and everything I have proof for it.
So Mimi I see you said you were gonna go live or something. I told you I gotta vet my shit out
I'm not gonna let have like some fucking bitch
Fucking guys dick that I didn't when I have like actual screenshots and receipts and proof that these guys like I mean
Who the fuck is saying that shit? It's never happened. I'm not fucking tree not golden. You dumb fucking bitch
Sorry
No, you're good. Yeah. Well, thank you that event yourself out, you know, I
Again as far as like the Christine and all that shit
I mean, I think it got blown out of the proportion, but I never gave you any background on what's
going on.
You're learning on your own.
No, you didn't.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm telling you, we've got people that are covering so many panels about this brand
and choose.
a crystal fucking shape that how the fuck am I the one to inform anybody everybody already knows
what's going on I don't need to tell anybody anything and I haven't even had time to fucking
talk to Mimi I didn't even know that if she would even be involved or ever intertwined in this
Anyways, yeah, I just wanted to come up really, you know really really fast. Thank you for coming up with me
I know you gotta go and do your thing. I'll listen. I
Literally, I was like so tired. I lost my sleep. It's like so fucked up to sit here and like here lies after lies about you, you know
I support almost everybody, you know, I'm like, okay, go to this person's channel, go to this, all of my, all of my, I did it even with, with Crystal, like that was the thing, which she literally was like, how do I do this and this and that and like, okay, teacher like kind of the ropes and then she was okay, everybody come to my safe place, okay, do it, but at least when you go there, don't talk shit about me, just be grateful that I even like, you know,
Uh, I don't know. I let you bring that fucking bush to drama because I barely ever have to deal with carrot
I don't talk to them
I would get three-way calls and i'm like who's on the line. I don't want to talk to carrot. I really don't
And I've tried to talk to her, I've tried to get her like for years to calm down and be a better person and she made these fake promises and it never worked.
So I gave up. Wait months and months ago. Crystal just gave up three days ago because of Brandon Q and other people. Figure that one out.
Thank you, MSW. Thank you for the sweet message too. I saw that earlier.
Yeah, there is no link. I mean, it's kind of late. I'm about
What crystal? Well, I don't think lying about people is winning
I don't think being a total fucking lunatic that oh, you know what else she said
She said that I made up a rumor about her getting 51 50. That's not true. That was Barb
I stood up for her. I thought people know this. These are these are actually our lives, you know, I was like, you know, she did it
the fuck crystal she never did that she never got 5150 it was barb that made it up but it's so
convenient for crystal and to fucking lie and that's the one that's a w just because you fucking lie
that's disgusting enjoy that thing but i wanted to come up really live and vent out i mean really
fast live and vent out and actually tell you guys like what just suggest of a little bit of what's
Pool of receipts I will provide it, but I will tell you one fucking thing you come with fucking receipts when you talk shit about me
Make up disgusting life and keep my fucking name out of your fucking
Downward fish mouth fucking mouth. I don't like you crystal and you're a fucking liar. I don't fuck with liars
Okay, wow
Okay, um anyone want to come up? I don't know here
Link more time
I guess beta got triggered by crystalline
Um, I know, I mean, if people will try to trigger you, I mean, it's like, yeah, I know, it's like, whatever, whatever, even Fawzi, Fawzi can't deal with this right now. Right. Good boy, Fawzi. Okay. Um, so hopefully everyone's having a good day. Someone come up.
I know we're gonna have different people coming up than maybe people are used to because
A lot of people have left, and so, but I think the right people left, you know, so they weren't sure what I did for people like, you know, I basically always let them promote their stuff and had them on talk to Dr. shit, you know, over and over hundreds of times.
Even them insulting me to my face and stuff like that, right.
But they want to.
overreact about the situation.
Think they know somebody grandstand, moral grandstand.
Oh, we look better.
Oh, it's popular.
Popular stand.
It's like, it's just the oldest trick in the book.
The people are falling for this oaky-doke, right?
Mm, bit.
And like I said, I had a pretty good live today, you know?
It's like over 40 people, which is like not too shabby,
you know?
Enjoy the chat. I'll be back later. I don't know. I'm a little bit. Maybe I'll take a blinker and pass out. You see
There you go
Me that's the other one one of them I got to turn on there you go. Oh, it's on that one turn on right now
The other one off to work on
Yeah, you have a good day too guys, and you know love yourself and each other. I'll see you soon. Okay?
Bye-bye